to us do you capitalize it I did I did
one word to one word yeah Vivian is my
father but we aren't happy anyway we
don't want to show for their product I
do want to show up in their product it's
honestly a great product this is a PEM
CAC error problem between user people
all right guys so well on our way to the
Baidu meetup in Sunnyvale
how many scobie's got 37 all right so
first off we're in late yeah we're late
now I will tell you why we're late the
scope is might like why we're late we
hired a new contractor for the machine
learning team hopefully he'll be
converting to full time in a few weeks
if things work out he'll be working on
driver monitoring so this is very very
exciting so we're on our way to Baidu in
Sunnyvale we're 30 minutes late we're
going on the Baidu Meetup we skipped the
wave on meetup yesterday because I heard
it was a total scam they they sent me an
email explicitly revoking my invitation
and then they sent one of our employees
three back and forth emails and
eventually revoked his invitation it was
basically just a scam to recruit but
we're hoping that by do is actually
going to be open because by do makes
open source stuff so open posit is
and don't say that these are users these
are using screen open pilot is the best
system you can get on your Honda or
Toyota vehicle that is definitely true
but once you've tried Cadillacs
supercruise you're gonna only want
supercruise I try to autopilot yeah it's
about the same as also violent but I've
tried supercruise and I'm like this is
what semi-autonomy should be this is a
great system except Viviane I'm gonna
try to engage it right now maybe show
them the batwing supercruise lock out
see owners back
so we think that GM remotely SSH tin to
our car and disabled - just kidding GM
can SSH into your car that's only Tesla
what actually happened is supercruise
disengaged something like vibrates you
see it it's like supercruise disengaging
and I was like I'm just gonna like let
it keep going like maybe it'll just keep
driving maybe it's like crap well just
start slowing down like all the time it
starts slowing down forcefully puts my
hazard lights on and then apparently if
I hadn't still touched it it would have
called OnStar but I touched it before it
called OnStar but not before I got super
cruise lockout see owners Minh so this
is a bit of a conundrum if I was the
only person in the car because I'm not
sure how I could read the owner's manual
I don't have super cruising vehicles
it's not smart of them but fortunately
Vivian's here and she read the owner's
manual and after about five minutes of
reading there were there were a lot of
pages we finally get to the part about
the super cruise lockout so what does it
say ignition without super cruise as
driving is terrible
basically we thought we had to restart
the car I told us wait to be sick I was
I had to restart the car and the owners
man and so we did what any sensible
person would do we restarted it really
where has the lights on in the middle of
I became to a full and complete stop
don't do rolling restarts we find that
came to a full and complete stop on the
highway dresser hazard it's right under
the glove box capacitive touch o Chemex
not against buttons this whole car is
covered in button is it that should be
an actual button I don't want to be able
to I'm fairly aware the one place they
should have a lock the old muffins they
get it some over and things like this
but the switch between
adaptive cruise control and normal
cruise control button
that's kind of nice actually sometimes I
wish that is it yeah sometimes I do wish
I is that really a button you want
honestly I've wanted it probably oh oh
look at this button the auto hold button
Auto hold that's important
what does it do it auto holds you so
this only breaks this I mean terrible no
I like that one come on it's not
necessarily could be just as easy to do
that can you do that oh can do yeah
but super cruise is great that's what I
was saying I know what it is but I don't
have super cruise right now we're gonna
I thought that car coming on that side
was actually the BMW time and I was like
it's way too just past those check it
out you know what's sad we could have
bought an m5 and I don't even get super
cruise right now I've been complaining
how much have I been compares open pilot
oh guys not engaged guys okay I've been
listening to this band Shinigami this is
actually just one guy and then like I
looked up like what is Shinigami mean
and I started watching Death Note it's
on Netflix you guys got to watch it the
old anime series on believe you're
probably the only person watching that
seriously it's it's so good it's so good
no but we're not here to talk about
Death Note we got to talk about
supercruise lockout what does this go be
saying actually they're not really con
they're not really
I should choose the rotation isn't kind
oh they don't like being 70 what do you
guys think about what are you my middle
school for real
that guy was your middle school day
Shinigami I think he's like 18 that you
like started a month ago maybe this
guy's death no maybe yeah yeah it's for
people like George who want to try to
see what the car yeah oh oh okay to
reset turn it off open close the door
lock the car wait at least a minute I
don't wait it this is worse than forcing
people to go through the Taco Bell
drive-thru to resume driving I would
honestly rather go through the Taco Bell
drive-thru that plane up there yeah yeah
it's got good wobble the realities got
ping-pong ping-pong
no but the reality is that you messed
that up you should have just taken
control I'll try to say like if this
lockout is this is harsher than
America's laws on drug possession you
know what I mean like this is just this
is just I was in control I just wanted
to see what would happen you know what I
mean the rules applied this is a
draconian rules
why dude a 2-speed kids work with the
Fords oh boy
ap does the same thing really it locks
you out ap once you want after the third
one what this one does to this one sit
on the third
well you clearly got alerted twice and
didn't do anything no I do what do you
mean an owner's manual but the other
gloves but the other ones I totally took
control well it says it gives you like a
1 2 3 a 1 2 3 it was a one time walking
you've been in the car the whole time
one thick Khan was rude what
how rude what do you say who is it rude
to me oh yeah don't tolerate that's the
route to me that's okay but don't be
rude to Vivian scope I thought okay you
can just restart Tesla pretty sure no
need to get out yeah nope Tessa really
give you three like I've seen the Tesla
holders he'll assist
I've turned it on that really needed a
button guys glad I had that button Oh
your poor that's a good deal
we I didn't even know you could and you
know a pilot worked on a $45,000 cars
I wasn't dollars it might have been a
different cards I hope you yeah and I
hope you didn't get you want I hope you
didn't buy a Ford it's not anymore
it's not
Oh Alexis no Alexis again and our exit
an rx-8 energy we're 45 oh you bought a
fusion energy I'm deeply sorry out of
Ford pilots never gonna work on for its
trade it in trade it in before the value
goes down you treated it you can use it
you can trade it in you don't lose that
much money do they know that our
particularly if your state has
reasonable tax laws we are over Ford we
are never gonna work on Florence the
gauntlet has been thrown down no far all
right that's it's go fees let's just
leave them with one more wouldn't it be
nice if I have super cruise right now oh
no super cruises locked out oh that's
right oh yeah open pilots gonna do that
same to you guys so always pay
attention when you drop me
I don't just test it open pilot doesn't
mess around